<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<sst xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/spreadsheetml/2006/main" count="136" uniqueCount="123"><si><t>Questions</t></si><si><t>Answers</t></si><si><t>college</t></si><si><t>airport</t></si><si><t>20 KM</t></si><si><t>chancellor</t></si><si><t>sad</t></si><si><t>vice chancellor</t></si><si><t>Vise chancellor of Maharana Pratap University of Agriculture and Technology, Udaipur is Dr.  Narendra  Singh  Rathore</t></si><si><t>mp</t></si><si><t>Ohh, you are feeling sad, so lets play a game or you can ask any thing from me</t></si><si><t>MPUAT Udaipur is Maharana Pratap University of Agriculture and Technology Udaipur. It is one of the leading agriculture universities of Rajasthan, India. Also, MPUAT Udaipur is  the second largest Agricultural University of the state, came into existence on 1st November, 1999 by bifurcation of the Rajasthan Agricultural University, Bikaner through promulgation of Government of Rajasthan Ordinance No. 6 of 1999, which became an Act in May, 2000.</t></si><si><t>Intranet Incharge</t></si><si><t>University Road, Pahada, Udaipur, Rajasthan, India</t></si><si><t>It is near college main building on main road opposite to First year block</t></si><si><t>It is adjacent to first year block opposite to college canteen on main road</t></si><si><t>It is adjacent to library on main road opposite to college canteen</t></si><si><t>It is about 200 meters from canteen to the left of the main road and opposite to new hostel building</t></si><si><t>It is near electrical engineering department at about 100 meters</t></si><si><t>It is located next to the mechanical engineering department and on the back side of civil engineering department</t></si><si><t>It is located opposite to the main college building on the main road, can reach there through stairs on the left side of the main road</t></si><si><t>It is located near farm machinery department and AVP hall in the main college building</t></si><si><t>It is located near computer science and IT department in the main building of the college</t></si><si><t>It is located opposite to the university new auditorium near instructional farms and post  harvesting technology unit of the college.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">It is located at near sunder vaas side gate of the university at about 300 meters on the road from MV hostel to the sunder vaas gate of the university via residential colony of university. </t></si><si><t>It is in the main building of the college near college library</t></si><si><t>College hostels are opposite to staff colony of university in the back side of the college main building</t></si><si><t>It is adjacent to chief warden residence near staff residential colony at walking distance from hostels on the road to sunder vaas gate of the university</t></si><si><t>udaipur</t></si><si><t>maharana</t></si><si><t>university</t></si><si><t>The College of Technology and Engineering (CTAE), Udaipur  is a constituent college of the Maharana Pratap University of Agriculture and Technology, Udaipur. The college was established in 1964. Presently the CTAE has undergraduate degree programmes in 7 branches, M.Tech. programmes in 10 disciplines, besides PhD programmes in 10 disciplines.
The college has been recognized as Outstanding Engineering College in Northern Region and has been awarded “Outstanding Institution Award” in 2013 by National Institute of Technical Teachers Training and Research, Chandigarh.</t></si><si><t>programmes</t></si><si><t>courses</t></si><si><t>The University offers various degree programme in engineering approved by AICTE and ICAR as follows:
1. four year under graduate engineering in Agriculture Engineering 55 seats, Civil Engineering 40 seats, Computer Science and engineering 60 seats, Electrical engineering 60 seats, Electronics and Communication engineering 60 seats, Mechanical engineering 40 seats, mining engineering 20 seats.
2. Also offers M Tech and PhD programmes in FMPE, RES, SWE, PFE, Civil Engineering, Computer Science and engineering, Electrical engineering, Electronics and Communication engineering, Mechanical engineering, and mining engineering.</t></si><si><t>The contact number of Dean is 0 2 9 4 2 4 7 0 8 3 7</t></si><si><t>contact number of dean</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">The email id of dean ctae is  ctaedean@gmail.com </t></si><si><t>email id of dean</t></si><si><t>The website address are, www.mpuat.ac.in,www.ctae.ac.in</t></si><si><t>The college has nine hostels and one scientist hostel providing homely atmosphere and appropriate environment for studies and aesthetic living. All hostels are equipped with water purifier, Aquaguard  water cooler, TV, Geyser and well furnished common room. WiFi  Internet facility is  also provided to the students in all hostels for 24 hours.</t></si><si><t>hostel facility</t></si><si><t>head of Electronics</t></si><si><t>head of mechanical</t></si><si><t>head of mining</t></si><si><t>head of Farm</t></si><si><t>head of Renewable</t></si><si><t>head of Food</t></si><si><t>engineering college</t></si><si><t>who is governor</t></si><si><t>who is Dean</t></si><si><t>where is student section</t></si><si><t>where is clinic</t></si><si><t>who is controller of examination</t></si><si><t>who is director research</t></si><si><t>who is UG coordinator</t></si><si><t>who is PG coordinator</t></si><si><t>where is farm</t></si><si><t>where is renewable energy</t></si><si><t>where is first year</t></si><si><t>where is Library</t></si><si><t>where is engineering</t></si><si><t>hostel</t></si><si><t>who is registrar</t></si><si><t>who is comptroller</t></si><si><t>who is librarian</t></si><si><t>where is computer science</t></si><si><t>where is electrical</t></si><si><t>where is mechanical</t></si><si><t>where is mining</t></si><si><t>where is civil</t></si><si><t>where is college canteen</t></si><si><t>Chief of Training</t></si><si><t>head of Soil</t></si><si><t>head of Basic</t></si><si><t>head of electrical</t></si><si><t>head of civil</t></si><si><t>head of computer</t></si><si><t>who is Vice chancellor</t></si><si><t>where is university</t></si><si><t>who is chief warden</t></si><si><t>where is electronics</t></si><si><t>I U M S Incharge</t></si><si><t>C T A E</t></si><si><t>CTAE</t></si><si><t>website</t></si><si><t>who is Sports Incharge</t></si><si><t>The College of Technology and Engineering (CTAE), Udaipur  is a constituent college of the Maharana Pratap University of Agriculture and Technology, Udaipur. The college was established in 1964. Presently the CTAE has undergraduate degree programmes in 7 branches, M.Tech. programmes in 10 disciplines, besides PhD programmes in 10 disciplines. The college has been recognized as Outstanding Engineering College in Northern Region and has been awarded “Outstanding Institution Award” in 2013 by National Institute of Technical Teachers Training and Research, Chandigarh.</t></si><si><t>Dean is Doctor P K Singh</t></si><si><t>Head of mechanical department is, Doctor M A Saloda</t></si><si><t>Head of mining department is, Doctor Anupam Bhatanagar</t></si><si><t>Head of farm department is, Doctor Ajay Sharma</t></si><si><t>Head of renewable energy department is, Doctor N L Panwar</t></si><si><t>Head of basic science is, Doctor A K Chittora</t></si><si><t>Head of soil department is, Doctor Mahesh Kothari</t></si><si><t>Head of food department is, Doctor N. K. Jain</t></si><si><t>Chief of training is, Doctor Vinod Yadav</t></si><si><t>Intranet inchnarge is, Doctor Sunil Joshi</t></si><si><t>I uM S incharge is, Doctor Sunil Joshi</t></si><si><t>Governor of rajasthan is, Honourable Shri Kalraj ji Mishra</t></si><si><t>Director of research is, Doctor S K Sharma</t></si><si><t>Registrar is, Mrs Kavita Pathak</t></si><si><t>Comptrolloer is, Mrs Manju Jain</t></si><si><t>U G Coordinator is, Doctor S C  Jain</t></si><si><t>P G Coordinator is, Doctor Navneet Agarwal</t></si><si><t>Controller of examination is, Doctor S K Intodiya</t></si><si><t>Chief Warden is, Doctor M K Khediya</t></si><si><t>Librarian is,Doctor Naveen Jain</t></si><si><t>Sports Inscharge is, Shri K B Sahay</t></si><si><t>The fee for B Tech, M tech and PhD programmes under self-finance courses is, rupee 35830 per semester.For government aided seats the fee is, rupee 15830 per semester.For more details please contact Mr Sohan Mali in student section of college.</t></si><si><t>what is fee stracture</t></si><si><t>fee</t></si><si><t>fee stracture</t></si><si><t>Head of Computer Science and Engineering Department is, Doctor Naveen Choudhary. His contact number is 0 2 9 4 2 4 7 0 3 0 5</t></si><si><t>The Vice chancellor of the University is, Honourable Doctor Narendra Singh Ji Rathore. His office contact number is, 0 2 9 4 2 4 6 0 7 7 3</t></si><si><t>Head of Civil Engineering Department is Doctor Trilok Gupta. His contact number is 9 4 1 4 4 0 6 2 2 3.</t></si><si><t>Head of electronics department is, Doctor Suneel Joshee. His contact number is, 0  29 4 2 4 7 1 6 3 1</t></si><si><t>Head Electrical Engineering Department is Doctor R R Joshee. His contact number is 0 2 9 4 2 4 7 0 8 0 8.</t></si><si><t>who is student welfare</t></si><si><t>Student welfare officer of university is Doctor sudheer jain and student welfare officer of college is Doctor Jay kumar meharchandaani.</t></si><si><t xml:space="preserve">who is I C A R </t></si><si><t>I C A R Nodal officer of M P U A T is  Doctor Lokesh Gupta</t></si><si><t>who is head of computer</t></si></sst>